(aircraft engine rumbling)
("I Want It That Way")
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ You are ♪
♪ My fire ♪
♪ The one desire ♪
♪ Believe ♪
♪ When I say ♪
♪ I want it that way ♪
♪ But we ♪
♪ Are two worlds apart ♪
♪ Can't reach to your heart ♪
♪ When you say ♪
♪ That I want it that way ♪
♪ Tell me why ♪
♪ Ain't nothin' but a heartache ♪
♪ Ain't nothin' but a mistake ♪
♪ Tell me why ♪
♪ I never wanna hear you say ♪
♪ I want it that way ♪
♪ Am I ♪
♪ Your fire ♪
♪ Your one desire ♪
♪ Yes, I know ♪
♪ It's too late ♪
♪ But I want it that way ♪
♪ Tell me why ♪
♪ Ain't nothin' but a heartache ♪
♪ Ain't nothin' but a mistake ♪
♪ Tell me why ♪
♪ I never wanna hear you say ♪
♪ I want it that way ♪
♪ Now I can see that we've fallen apart ♪
♪ From the way that it used to be, yeah ♪
♪ No matter the distance,
I want you to know ♪
♪ That deep down inside of me ♪
♪ You are ♪
♪ My fire ♪
♪ The one desire ♪
♪ You are you are, you are, you are ♪
♪ Don't wanna hear you say ♪
♪ Ain't nothin' but a heartache ♪
♪ Ain't nothin' but a mistake
don't wanna hear you say ♪
♪ I never wanna hear you say oh, yeah ♪
♪ I want it that way ♪
♪ Tell me why ♪
♪ Ain't nothin' but a heartache ♪
♪ Ain't nothin' but a mistake ♪
♪ Tell me why ♪
♪ I never wanna hear you say
don't wanna hear you say ♪
♪ I want it that way ♪
♪ Tell me why ♪
♪ Ain't nothin' but a heartache ♪
♪ Ain't nothin' but a mistake ♪
♪ Tell me why ♪
♪ I never wanna hear you say
don't wanna hear you say ♪
♪ I want it that way ♪
♪ 'Cause I want it that way ♪